addque.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy - AddQue

Your privacy is important to us, so Addque has created this Privacy Policy to explain how your information is protected, collected and used. This Privacy Policy applies to all Addque web sites, including our publicly accessible web sites located at Addque.com ("Addque"). This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. You can always review the most current version at http://www.addque.com/privacy-policy-p23. By using Addque, you consent to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and are aware that our policies may evolve in the future. If there is a conflict between our Terms of Use governing your use of the sites and this Privacy Policy, the Terms of Use control.

**Collection** : Information posted on Addque is obviously publicly available. Our servers are located in the United States and india . Therefore, if you choose to provide us with personal information, you are consenting to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers in the United States and india. We collect and store the following personal information:

*Email address, physical contact information, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information;

*Computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from Addque and ad data (all through cookies - you can take steps to disable the cookies on your browser although this is likely to affect your ability to use the site);

*Other information, including your IP address and standard web log information.

**Use:We use your personal information to** :

*Provide our services

*Resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;

*Encourage safe trading and enforce our policies;

*Customize the user experience, measure interest in our services, and inform users about services and updates;

*Communicate marketing and promotional offers to you;

*Do other things for users as described when we collect the information.

**Disclosure** : We don't sell or rent users' personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without users explicit consent. We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other's rights, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. We may also share personal

**Information with** :

*Corporate affiliates who help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and provide joint services. (Our corporate affiliates will market only to users who ask them to).

*Service providers who help with our business operations.

**Using Information from Addque** : You may use personal information gathered from Addque only to follow up with another user about a specific posting, not to send spam or collect personal information from someone who hasn't agreed to that.

**Access, Modification, and Deletion** : You can see, modify or erase your personal information by reviewing your posting or account status page. Contact customer support (support@addque.com ) to review any personal information we store that is not available on Addque. There may be a charge associated with such requests but these will not exceed the amounts permitted by law. We delete personal information when we no longer need it for the purposes we described earlier. We retain personal information as permitted by law to resolve disputes, enforce our policies; and prevent offenders from coming back.

**Security** : We use many tools (encryption, passwords, physical security) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. We can't however guarantee the continuous functionality and liability of these tools at all times.

**General** : We may update this policy at any time, with updates taking effect when you next post or after 30 days, whichever is sooner. If we or our corporate affiliates are involved in a merger or acquisition, we may share personal information with another company, but this policy will continue to apply. Send questions about this policy to privacy@addque.com .
